Here comes the trump card.
The princess has arrived.
Step aside, everyone!
He just wants to drink mine.
I'm telling you.
She's mine.
What are you looking at?
It's mine.
Mine.
Get lost.
Because I only allow my heart to be your resting place.
My love is just that dangerous.
I'm the perfect gentleman.
Come on.
Did I give you a bit too much freedom?
I'm busy all day long.
I have 365 people to care for 365 days a year.
Viper of a woman.
How dare you!
Close your eyes.
So we closed them.
Xia Da.
I'm telling you.
Today, I...
just pushed him.
You tuck your tail and run when you see me.
Why aren't you kneeling before the Crown Prince?
Go ahead and take a shot.
Who are you?
You pick and you pay.
Pay first.
Authentic or not, you have to pay.
Hmph.
I'm not listening.
Delivery guy.
Just stay right there.
Look at how much He Yiwei eats.
And works so hard.
Want some?
Miss.
Can you fill it up a bit more for me?
Do you want a piece?
Come try this.
It's delicious.
Silk stocking milk tea.
You.
I picked multiple.
Are you really that hungry?
Grab something to drink.
He.
Listen to them.
As long as you treat me, that's enough.
Just believe there's ice cream waiting for us.
Let me see if we can eat well.
Zhang Jiawei is looking for food again.
Bring some food and drinks over here.
Bring some drinks over here.
What the hell is this?
This is super high in calories.
Real fruit actually has the most calories.
My meal card.
You stepped on my meal card.
This is my favorite.
I absolutely love this.
I love eating it plain.
Can't you buy your own food in Hengdian?
Can any of you guys help me twist this?
Hey.
Up there, up there.
You're my teammate.
I already know what you are.
You didn't...
He definitely mentioned the laser pointer.
Those two are in it together.
They have the same information.
It could be a decoration.
This right here changes the direction of this door.
It's not math.
It connects the maze.
This door can slide over here.
Then the inside becomes a passageway.
The killer never even came in.
One of you four stabbed him right here in the back.
It's about emotion.
There's no logic to it.
Emotions don't follow logic.
The outside window doesn't align with the sealed one inside.
He found these two windows using the female tourist's arm span.
No, no, no.
Ning.
The killer didn't expose their identity to confuse people.
It was to make them think Luo Ding is just one person.
Let's have a drink and give ourselves a round of applause!
That's incredible!